I can't front. At first, I was like, y'all are taking this insecure thing too far. Like,
it's, I mean, it's my experience. Otherwise, it felt like, what's the point? However,
seeing the visceral response from fans brought me all the way back to when I took the Black
Popular Culture class that Professor Donna Aene Davis taught at SUNY Purchase. And she really
drilled home that art for Black folks, particularly in the United States, is not simply just about
entertainment. It is political because it is our representation and in our own voice
that is something that we rarely get. So our characters and our stories are not simply just
meant to entertain. They are literally meant as proof of life. And so that made me say, okay,
I need to talk about this further, but in a greater context. Let's talk about the difference between
lack and abundance. A lack conversation is why would Amanda expect to be invited to the insecure
reunion? An abundance conversation is why were amends not made so that Amanda would be present at the
insecure reunion? Ultimately, a reunion tour for a TV show would be all about pleasing the fans of that
show. That's the goal. And I would suggest that the fans of a show want to see the characters that
they have aligned with. There are many people who have said they didn't give a damn about Tiffany.
However, I know because I experienced it on a regular basis. There are so many women in particular,
mothers in particular, who very much aligned with Tiffany's journey through postpartum depression
and really connected with me in person to say thank you for portraying that in such a realistic way.
Which is also why, you know, the performance of stories on speed on screen is so imperative because
people, humans, we need to be seen. On a larger scale, I'm always thinking of how do I show up in
abundance versus lack. I didn't always think that way. However, as I have grown, particularly in the last
three years, spiritually, intellectually, communally, that has definitely been a shift. And the difference
between lack and abundance is important because lack is patriarchal and it deals with the failure to
see growth, to see expansion on a communal level. So abundance, on the other hand, is matriarchal
and is about restoration. And so the difference is imperative to how we even view our role in
resistance on a much bigger scale. While I have you, if you'd like to hear me talk about things
on a abundance level, you can check out my new radio show on Tavis Smiley's KBLA Talk 1580. I'll be
there every Friday with the Summer of Seals from 12 to 2 p.m. Pacific and 4 to 6 p.m. Pacific. And you can
check me out by downloading the KBLA Talk 1580 radio app or listening on YouTube. Hope to see you there
or hear you there, I should say, where we can talk about abundance and how to get out of the
lack state that this capitalist imperialist empire has got us in.